THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
What is...
going on?
Oh, I...
We just look like a couple
in their talking stage
having spent the night together.
But why is he there?
Oh! I went out for some fresh air.
Oh, right! Right by the cafe.
We said we'd go
for a second round of drinks, right?
Are you guys detectives?
You think going over what happened
will get you anywhere?
Be careful!
Watch your step!
One, two!
We’re almost there.
Wait!
Oh, gosh.
Are you kidding me?
Should I just leave him here?
No, don't leave without me.
You're like a puppy
with separation anxiety.
One, two, three!
- Ui-yeong!
- Hey, Ji-su.
What are you doing here?
Weren't you at the cafe? What?
I left something at the hotel.
I see.
Excuse me! Why are you sleeping
on her shoulder? Hey!
I'll take him to the hotel.
You're going to the hotel like that?
- Let's go.
- Huh?
Come. Unless you want to sleep here.
- Gosh!
- Wait!
- What a mess.
- Let's go.
- Oh, gosh.
- Man!
I'm thirsty...
Please give me some water, sir.
You're kidding.
Seriously.
Here.
- Cold!
- Are you serious?
You're a handful.
It's cold.
Let's go, Ui-yeong.
Are you sleeping?
This...
isn't right.
Gosh.
That hurts.
The drinks really got to her head, huh?
There's no way
I can leave these two alone.
THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
EPISODE 6
I'm sorry, you couldn't even go home
because of me.
It's fine. I'm okay.
What do you mean?
You can't just trust some guy
and go to his hotel room!
What would you have done without me?
I understand I owe you one
but I'm not the type
to cross boundaries
just because I'm drunk.
How do you know your drunk habits
when you don't know when you get drunk?
I almost thought
you were a freshman at a party.
A freshman?
Cut it out.
You're making him uncomfortable.
- And nothing happened. It's fine.
- Are you serious?
I'd better go
before people start showing up for work.
Take a shower first.
- You slept with him, after all.
- Hey!
We have a great shower room for employees.
Okay, go before people see you.
Okay, then.
Oh, wait.
Oh, right. Thanks.
I'm so sorry. I feel terrible.
Why don't we grab dinner this weekend?
Get whatever you want. My treat.
Oh...
Sure, then.
How about Saturday?
Sure, a dinner sounds great.
You owe me dinner, too.
You owe me a big one.
No, you owe me many big ones.
I already told you I would.
Let's decide when to meet over text.
Okay, have a good day at work.
Thanks.
Bye.
Are you seriously crazy?
What if someone saw you?
My gosh!
Hold on.
This is too peaceful.
She never caused any trouble
in her twenties.
What is she doing?
I wasted way too much energy
from the morning.
Maybe I should get some coffee.
What's this?
THE MAGIC OF A SURPRISE GIFT FOR YOU
WHO WANTS TO GO HOME
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING! - HYUN-MIN
Hyun-min's so cute sometimes.
Where are you, Ui-yeong?
Didn't I say it was common courtesy
to tell your rommate
if you weren't coming home?
I'm calling the cops
if you don't answer by 9 a.m.
WE HAD A STAFF PARTY
We had a staff party to celebrate
the new event
and it ended late,
so I just slept in the staff room.
Sorry.
That's my towel.
So, did you watch us two all night?
Don't you think that's a bit much?
You know what's a bit much?
You sleeping on Ui-yeong's shoulder.
How can a man be so weak to alcohol?
Don't try to change the topic.
I don't like
how you keep hanging around Ui-yeong.
You pretend to care,
but you just want a chance with her.
Hanging around her?
You look like a virgin.
Do you even know how to get a chance?
A virgin?
Hey.
- Huh?
- Oh!
Oh, this isn't what you think it is.
I saw nothing.
No need to explain your private life.
No, please let me.
Wait! There's been a misunderstanding!
Gosh.
Everyone knows everything around here.
. According to the witnesses
there wasn't just one man, but two!
I'm a little disappointed.
- Why?
- You can't date multiple people
if you're really in love.
No, you can be in love and still have fun!
Listen, Sae-byeok.
Our society is too close-minded
and old-fashioned.
They either think it's love or an affair.
That's why people get busted
while secretly cheating
embarrass themselves,
and ruin their careers!
Ui-yeong!
How long have you been there?
Oh, I just came in.
But...
don't you think that's a bit harsh?
Oh, I guess you don't believe rumors?
Hmm? What rumor?
"Despite being in her fifties,
Ms. S is still the queen of romance.
She always says she's in love with acting
but in fact, she's been head-over-heels
for someone lately!
She's in a common-law relationship
with a surgeon who used to be married
but has an affair with Mr. B,
a director, at a hotel
while being a sugar mommy to a model.
The scandal is only growing
with her complicated dating life."
The queen of romance?
Could that be Son Jeong-a?
It's pretty clear that it's her.
She recently checked into our hotel.
Really?
This hotel is
where she meets the director.
Mr. Jin says
he can't come to the meeting today.
He just married his wife.
He doesn't want her to get the wrong idea.
Is he only not coming today
or does he want me out of his movie?
Well...
What a wimp.
Sure, whatever.
Let's just grab dinner and go.
- You can sit.
- Okay.
Hello, I'm Kim Min-seong from Star A.
Why haven't you denied the rumor yet?
I don't want to add fuel to the fire
by being so rash.
I'll explain myself soon.
You shouldn't be following me
in my personal time.
- This is inappropriate.
- I'll sort it...
Hey! Don't you dare...
Dong-hoon!
could you please call the ambulance?
Here, you see a larva.
Follow the larva's outer layer,
which has been shed
and you'll find the larva in its pupa form
wrapped in his big blanket.
Stop it.
The pupae is finally coming out!
Am I going to be okay?
I think
my autonomic nervous system is broken.
Come out.
Hot!
I'VE NEVER SEEN MR. SONG LIKE THIS
It's not just your first hangover.
It's also your first time
waking up with one.
I have no right to say anything
if she rejects me.
I must've been out of my mind.
I should be doing my best to impress her.
Why did I drink when I know I can't?
It's already too late.
But she was drunk with you.
I'm sure she's worried
about the same thing. Don't worry.
Gosh, you're wasting so much food!
How can you not touch anything
your mom makes for you?
Aren't you seeing her on Saturday?
That's great.
Out with the old love, in with the new.
Forget the hangover with some soup
and make new memories
to forget about the old ones.
This is perfect.
So, what's the plan?
We'll get some good food
and watch the movie
we didn't watch last time.
It's all sorted, then!
What do you mean?
I have to start planning now.
I have to make sure
I make up for my drunk mess.
Hello!
Ms. Son Jeong-a will come here today.
Stay tuned for updates.
There are so many reporters here.
Man, this is a disaster.
I'll make sure to get good updates!
I guess I won't be going home anytime.
Why is the security so bad
when the condo's so expensive?
Too many celebrities live there.
I can't drive you around
with my leg like this.
You should just stay here for a bit.
It's trendy to prepare what to say
and all supporting documents
for one big press release these days.
Sure.
That's better than wasting all my time
answering trashy reporters everywhere.
I'm not young anymore.
I have nothing to lose.
Just find me a reporter
who will write a good article for me.
To beat a romance scandal
with greater love?
You're a genius.
You're sure no reporters can enter here,
right?
Don't worry.
Have you...
ever used
the Guest Relations Officer service?
No, what's that?
Simply put
it's a manager who will help you
with your stay here.
You'll be assigned one manager
to help you around
and get things for you. What do you think?
Oh! That sounds great!
Please choose a sharp female manager.
Okay, I'll look for one.
Enjoy your stay.
Can you believe it?
Did you see that article?
LIST OF FINALISTS
FOR THE HOSPITAL DIRECTOR POSITION
DR. SHIN JI-HUN OF SURGERY,
BORN IN 1968 (AGE 57)
HANKUK UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
You've been the talk of the town
all day today
and look! Speak of the devil.
I didn't think you'd be on celebrity news
instead of research news.
- Is that so?
- I'm happy
just to be
the Vice Director of the hospital
but everyone's been asking me
to run for Director
for the hospital's reputation.
I was wondering why, but now I know.
I guess gossping is fun.
Aren't you busy?
I didn't think you'd have time to gossip
right in the hallway,
chatting it up like a teenageer.
Looks like you're having fun.
I have a surgery, so please excuse me.
The door is closing.
SON JEONG-A
Did your check-in go smoothly?
I saw the news.
It's okay.
I didn't think it'd be easy to date
such a big star, anyway.
Should I meet you at the hotel
this weekend?
Hey, Mom. You didn't have dinner, right?
What's all this?
Ta-da!
It looks delicious.
Doesn't it taste amazing?
I know you're an adult, but sleep at home.
I'll change the door password
if you stay out again.
Don't say it like that.
Just tell me you were worried about me.
And say it nicely.
The balcony stinks
because of the big pile of recycling.
And we're out of clean towels.
And eggs!
You just want me to do the chores.
I just took out the recycling
and cleaned the floor!
And stop drinking.
You used to come home after a night out,
no matter how drunk you were.
Right? I was so good.
I always make sure to come home, so why...
You can't go.
What's wrong? You're scaring me.
- Huh?
- What?
- Hmm?
Looks like your memory's back.
It already smells amazing.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Anytime.
So
I want you
to be the Guest Relations Officer
for Ms. Son.
Isn't that for the Concierge Team?
As you know, we don't have a manual
for the position.
So, all you have to do is
build a good rapport
and provide the best service possible.
I'm not sure if I'll be good.
You know what I always say.
The best kind of service
doesn't come from expertise.
It comes from the heart.
You'll do great.
Buying things for her is your main task
but more importantly
the public is too cold toward her.
And you're her fan.
I thought it'd be nice for her
to be around someone who likes her.
I see.
You can fangirl in person.
Okay, got it.
Great.
I'll set up the basics
but ask her what else she needs
and get them for her.
- Yes, sir.
- If you have any questions
call the manager.
This is his business card.
But remember
work is work.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Sure.
"EVERY PRODUCTION IS LIKE HER LAST
FOR THE ROMANCE QUEEN OF 20 YEARS"
JEONG-A IS BACK ON SCREEN
AFTER A LONG BREAK WITH THE NEW MOVIE
I'M A BIG READER LIKE SEON-HYE
MY FAVORITE WRITER IS MARGUERITE DURAS
I LIKE ENJOYING SOME WINE AND CHEESE
AFTER WORK
SON JEONG-A'S CONTROVERSIAL AWARD SPEECH!
SHE'S NOTHING WITHOUT LOVE?
CHECK OUT SON JEONG-A'S SPEECH
I feel most alive when I'm acting
and when I'm in love.
And I've never been ashamed
of my emotions.
I'm nothing without love.
My goal is to continue portraying
different kinds of love in my acting.
Thank you.
ACTRESS OF THE YEAR, SON JEONG-A
Congratulations.
I see.
This was why it was controversial.
My gosh!
When did you two get here?
Loving your junior colleagues is
also love!
What if you end up hating her
at the end of this?
Rumors say she only talks to men.
- What?
No way.
Don't you two have work to do?
Talking about celebrities is fun, huh?
This was the highlight of my day.
Back to work!
I have an update for you.
One of the pop-up display cases is wobbly.
Should I call HOME and ask about repairs?
- Yeah, please do.
- Okay.
Is it true that you use
seasonal ingredients in the soup?
Oh, peas? Okay.
I'll book a table for two
at 5:30 p.m. on the 2nd.
I'd like a table in a quiet section
for us to talk, please.
Okay, thank you.
There's a 46% chance of rain
in the afternoon.
I'll bring an umbrella, just in case.
A TABLE FOR TWO AT 5:30 P.M.,
PEA SOUP, PACK AN UMBRELLA
Check this out.
- Hey.
What's Mr. Song doing?
No idea. Maybe he's started a new project?
You could say he's started
the biggest project of his life.
You guys need to go to the hotel
with a toolbox.
- The hotel?
- One of the display cases is wobbly.
Check on all the furniture
while you're there.
I'll go!
- I can do it.
- You?
You don't need to do everything,
but thanks!
No worries.
See you.
So, we don't need to go?
- Ui-yeong.
- Tae-seop!
You came to fix it yourself?
Yeah, how are you?
I'm good.
Do you remember Ms. Son Jeong-a?
- Yeah.
- I'm her manager at the hotel
or something like that now.
Really? I know you love her.
Yeah, so I'm a little on edge.
I've read all articles about her
and even studied her social media pages.
Her social media?
Do you use them?
Yeah.
How do I fix this?
It's like I'm looking through her drawers.
She's a foodie.
CAFE TOUR
My gosh.
You're surely having a lot of fun
snooping around her drawers.
Ui-yeong is mostly in charge
of purchasing ingredients for the hotel
so she's probably been
to all the best restaurants in Seoul.
She won't be impressed
with just any restaurant, then.
Should I find another place?
Close her drawers for now.
Look at this one first.
It keeps dragging on the floor.
Oh, right.
- Can I see it?
- Yeah, I'll step aside.
Didn't you say it was expensive marble
imported from Italy?
Yeah, could you hold it like this?
- Like this?
- Yeah.
All good.
Are you that excited about the date?
It's our one-and-only first date.
I'm getting more excited
now that I've planned so much.
Gosh.
WELCOME SON JEONG-A
WE HOPE YOU A COMFORTABLE AND JOYFUL STAY
This should be enough.
One more thing, though.
I'm Lee Ui-yeong.
I'll be helping you during your stay.
Nice to meet you. I'm Son Jeong-a.
Please look around and let me know anytime
if you need anything.
Oh?
Wow, I've been reading this book.
You love this author, right?
I thought I'd prepare her newest book.
But you beat me.
I got it as soon as it was out.
I see.
Hotels usually prepare fresh flowers.
Did you purposely put
a photo of them instead?
You're allergic to flowers.
ACTRESS OF THE YEAR, SON JEONG-A
MAYBE ALLERGIC TO POLLEN?
I've never told anyone that
in fear that they'd think I was picky.
But you noticed before I told you.
So
what do you think about the rumor?
Do you think it's true?
Well...
Among the three guys
who do you think is my real love?
I believe
my role is to make your stay at our hotel
as comfortable and relaxing as possible.
Mr. Eun picked
such a smart person for the job.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
Oh, and I always drink
two cups of coffee per day.
But the coffee at the hotel is
too bitter for me
so could you get me
some more fruity beans?
I'll prepare
some light-medium roast beans.
I'll probably also need a few more pajamas
and an extra humidifier, please.
Okay, noted.
PREPARE A DRIP COFFEE SET
AND LIGHT-MEDIUM ROAST BEANS
Next, a drip set
and light-medium roast beans.
Oh, no, I'd better get going.
We're closing soon.
- Hey.
- What?
You're just a small stage director.
Whiskey isn't your thing.
Are you here to say something?
You saw right through me.
You know the performance this weekend?
Yeah, it's for Seungbo Group,
the theater's sponsor company, right?
I need you to perform.
Se-hyeon had to go to his hometown
becauase his mother is ill.
What happened to her?
She's just really ill.
See you at the rehearsal tomorrow.
- You're leaving already?
- Yeah.
The whiskey tastes too fancy.
Okay, see you.
We're really closed... Oh?
Can I get some drip coffee?
With fruity beans?
Sure, come in.
- Were you working until now?
- Yeah, I had a lot to do.
Aren't you a bit hungry?
Mom, I'm grabbing a bite
after working until late.
- Here.
- I can't drink for a while.
Why not?
I have work tomorrow
and my mom's been unhappy with me.
By the way, are we allowed to eat here?
Of course. Should we play some music?
Sure, sounds good.
It's nice to have a friend
who works at a cafe.
Hey
this is one of the three meals
I've promised you, okay?
I can't believe you're keeping a tally.
This is nothing compared
to what I've done for you.
No, you're clearly enjoying it.
You got some sauce there.
And you were the one who volunteered.
You can't tell me to pay you back
when you volunteeered.
I guess so.
You're right.
You got some on your face, too.
I'm not the type to be
all up in anyone's business
but I can't stop being nosy around you.
See?
Don't do that to people.
That could lead them on.
You're always so weirdly close.
I wouldn't exactly say
you're getting the wrong idea.
Huh?
You seem to think I don't mean anything
but we went on a blind date
even though I was filling in
for someone else.
And we're becoming closer.
I've been having fun since the first day.
Don't you feel the same?
Hmm?
It's nothing serious.
You know
you make my life interesting these days.
Just keep eating.
Eat first, and take your time
to digest it all.
How are you getting home?
I called a cab. It should be here soon.
I have to go to my rehearsal now.
- Get home safely.
- Okay.
Let's grab another meal sometime.
Sure, bye.
See you.
What was that about?
Does he like me,
or do I just make his life interesting?
SONG TAE-SEOP HAS REPLIED TO YOUR STORY
GOOD WORK TODAY.
I CAN'T WAIT FOR SATURDAY. GOODNIGHT
Good work today.
I can't wait for Saturday.
Goodnight.
LEE UI-YEONG
Thanks, goodnight to you, too.
See you soon!
- Come in.
- Okay.
- I'm just on the phone.
Hey.
What about the casting?
Why would you do something
I didn't even ask for?
The performance is just for the employees.
I'm the wife of the CEO.
Can't you be more supportive?
Whatever. I can't go.
Dr. Shin's coming tomorrow.
I need to have a long talk with him.
It's already giving me a headache.
Just send me the address.
Okay, will do.
I just have a favor to ask you.
Sure, what is it?
Could you bring a bouquet
to an address I give you tomorrow?
It's an important show, but I can't go.
And...
- this is the card for the bouquet.
- Okay.
No need to watch the show.
Just deliver the bouquet for me.
Okay, then.
And I'd like to invite a friend here
for dinner tomorrow.
How many of them?
Just one.
He'll arrive at the hotel around 7 p.m.
Could you prepare something Western
that goes with wine?
Sure, we'll prepare the dinner
as soon as your guest arrives.
He'll also be sleeping over.
Please make sure
the security is extra strong.
Okay, will do.
Should we have gotten two?
Will this be enough?
Your uncle isn't that greedy with food.
Or anything, for that matter.
Are you sure he's not greedy?
Is this the wrong house?
Wet wipes.
Hydrogen peroxide.
Band-aids. Are you going to a boot camp?
Blanket.
Are you sure you're going on a date?
I don't know what might happen
on the date.
And they're all useful to have, anyway.
Sua, go wash your hands.
Let's eat the pizza.
Okay.
I've never seen a guy prepare so much
for a date.
Are you nervous or just crazy?
I'm just excited.
Dad! Look at this!
A timetable?
PICK UP EUI-YEONG AT 5 P.M.
DINNER FROM 5:30 TO 7 P.M.
COFFEE FROM 7 TO 7:30 P.M.
This isn't a dream, is it?
I thought guys like him
only existed in dreams.
Sua, can you help me pick out my outfit
after we eat?
Sure.
Sua, I'm better than him, right?
Not a chance. He's a million times better.
Hey, that hurts!
Sorry, I thought it was a dream.
Keep eating.
DEUKGEUN DEUKGEUN GYM
Isn't it so hot today?
That just proves
we worked really hard today.
No, I think
the air conditioners are broken.
What are you talking about?
We just fixed them.
What? They're really not working.
See?
It would've been cheaper
to get new ones at this point!
Hello?
Hi, Hyun-min.
Seung-jun! I'm off early today.
We can meet earlier.
But my gym's air conditioners are broken.
I need to fix them...
I don't think I can leave the gym.
Oh, no.
Isn't it too hot in there
without air conditioning?
Yeah, it feels like a sauna.
Gosh, I can't even breathe.
Let me fix this and get back to you.
- Okay.
- I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
DEUKGEUN DEUKGEUN GYM
It's too hot, right? I'm so sorry.
Sorry. Here's a fresh towel.
Sorry, it's too hot, isn't it?
- I know it's hot.
- Here's a towel.
Here's a towel.
It feels like a boot camp here.
Even my underwear is drenched.
Sorry.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I'll give you an extention on your pass.
Sorry.
Let's cool down.
Hyun-min!
- It's hot, right? Here.
- Thank you.
Which one would you like?
Thank you.
Wait.
You look familiar.
Don't we know each other from somewhere?
- Well...
- Don’t worry about your membership.
I'm not sure.
That's a bit much.
- No, that's not it.
- Seriously.
It's a lot of sweat.
Let me give you an extra towel.
Thanks.
I'm out!
Okay, see you.
CLOSED OVER THE WEEKEND
TO FIX THE AIR CONDITIONERS
Seung-jun! Take a break.
Sure.
He's so hard-working.
Here.
Thanks for today.
How did you know to come here?
It's written right on your shirt.
"Deukgeun Deukgeun."
I can still remember you
taking that shirt off.
You're a sicko.
But you like them.
Is that strawberry-flavored?
Let me have a bite.
It's still a date...
Something bright.
Let's see.
No, if I dress up too much
I'll look like a rookie.
How about this one? Or this?
Or jeans?
Alright.
Perfect.
This looks casual but nice.
MEORU ART CENTER
Thank you.
- Enjoy the show.
- Thank you.
- Here.
- Hello.
- Enjoy the show.
- Thank you.
- Hello.
- Could you deliver these to someone?
Of course, you can leave it with me,
and I'll give it to the person.
Who is it for?
Oh, give me a sec.
DEAR JI-SU,
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR SHOW
Ji-su?
Oh, you mean Mr. Shin Ji-su?
Oh...
Yeah, Mr. Shin Ji-su.
Okay.
- Thank you.
Hello, may I see your tickets?
- Enjoy the show.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
THE SEAGULL
So, he knows Jeong-a?
Is it...
MS. S, THE QUEEN OF ROMANCE,
IS THE QUEEN OF SCANDALS?
THE QUEEN'S MANY MEN...
"She's in a common-law relationship
with Dr. A, a surgeon who had a wife
but has an affair with Mr. B,
a director, at a hotel
while being a sugar mommy to a model."
THE SCANDAL IS ONLY GROWING
WITH HER COMPLICATED DATING LIFE
Hey, Ui-yeong.
Your hairstyle's changed.
And where are your glasses?
I thought I'd dress up a bit.
It's our first date, after all.
I should've dressed up more, too.
You look as beautiful as always.
"As always"?
Ready for dinner?
I found a restaurant nearby.
A one-star Michelin chef
recently opened it.
It's closed.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE HAD TO CLOSE
DUE TO A DEATH IN THE CHEF'S FAMILY
Oh, they're closed...
I also prepared an alternative,
just in case.
It's a five-minute walk.
I didn't book a table,
but it's still early
so I'm sure we can get a seat.
Ms. Lee Ui-jin?
- Is Ms. Lee Ui-jin here?
- Here!
You can come in.
We're going to be late for the movie
if we wait for a table here.
Oh, then...
Well...
Tae-seop
I know it's not a romantic place
but I have a favorite restaurant nearby.
You want to go there with me?
That sounds good.
Okay.
- The table's a bit wobbly, right?
- Yeah.
Be careful, it's hot.
Thank you.
- Careful.
- Thank you.
You can move tables if it bothers you.
No, it's fine.
I can't believe I'm here with you.
I'm only ever here with my colleagues
because there's a client nearby.
I see.
This looks great.
Let's eat.
Huh?
Oh, this stops me from burning my tongue
and lets me eat faster.
I see.
Like this.
Watch out.
Thank you.
Go on. Try it.
- It's amazing.
- Right?
I'm glad you like it.
It's so good.
Thank you.
Oh, hold on a sec.
Great.
- All good.
You're pretty good at that.
It's nothing.
No, it was impressive.
How did you start designing furniture?
My family didn't have a dining table
for some time
because we suddenly became poor.
But it wasn't just the table
that was taken from us.
We stopped eating together
or talking to each other.
We became distant from each other.
That was when I realized
furniture wasn't just an object.
It was from that point on
that I realized it was so important.
And I wanted to do something important
because I was in my twenties.
I see.
I worked nonstop
since starting my business.
How were you in your twenties?
You're so bubbly.
You must've been so social.
No, I only had a handful.
I wasn't well-off
in my younger years, either
so I only ever thought about myself.
I thought everyone should live a hard life
because I was living one.
I didn't know you ever had a hard time.
I don't have all that many fond memories.
I never went on any trips
and rejected every guy,
saying I didn't have time to date.
I see. That's okay.
You can enjoy all of that now.
That's right.
That's why I like how things are now.
I'm glad we met now.
Humans are funny.
But I want to trust him one more time.
Why are you crying?
Are you that sad?
No, it's my eyes.
Do they hurt?
Let's get out.
Even after having been betrayed once
I can't help but give him another chance.
- Are you alright?
- Yeah.
I'm not used to wearing contact lenses.
I think something got in my eye.
It stings.
It looks pretty serious.
It's really red. Look at me.
What? No...
Let me look.
This won't do. Take your lenses out first.
Are you better?
Did you take them out? How is it?
Much better.
Should we head back in?
Where?
You can't even see anything.
Let's watch it another time.
You should go home.
No, I can't.
We have to watch the movie today.
But you can't even see properly.
Then...
Oh, do you want to watch it at my house?
Your house?
No, I don't mean it like that.
I just don't want to say
"Next time" again.
Oh.
Should we get some popcorn, too?
Yeah.
Oh.
Hold my arm and follow me.
Okay.
The chauffeur should be here soon.
Sorry. I have a license,
but I've never driven a car.
It's okay.
Oh?
I love this song.
- Same.
- Really?
Bravo!
You were amazing!
- Good work today.
- You too.
- Good work.
- Good job.
- Good work!
- Congrats!
- Good job.
Ji-su, this is for you.
Don't forget it.
Okay.
Congratulations on your show.
I have big news for you.
Please meet me at The Hills.
MEORU ART CENTER
Mr. Shin.
I'm Kim Ji-yeong, a reporter for Daily N.
You're the model mentioned
in the rumor about Ms. Son, right?
How do you know Ms. Son?
I have nothing to do with her.
Please never approach me again.
We've confirmed that the biggest sponsor
for the theater is Seungbo Group.
The wife of the Group's CEO is
Ms. Son's best friend. Did you know that?
I hear she's far more than an advisor
when it comes to investing in the arts.
What?
I'm just wondering
if you maybe made a deal with her
in exchange for this sponsorship.
That was so awesome.
Hey!
Ji-su! What are you doing?
- You bastard!
- Are you crazy?
You asked me get on stage on purpose.
Yeah, how else?
You know that's not what I mean.
You've been paying me
with the money you get from Jeong-a!
How could you insult me like this?
The CEO's wife is sponsoring us
because she loves our show.
Yeah? Why would they invest in a show
that doesn't turn a profit?
And the wife's never even come
to watch our show.
Stop acting
like an arrogant and childish bastard.
It's not about paying you.
It's about paying the rent, the cast
for the stage outfits, food, and props!
We've dedicated our lives to this
and we'll do anything to perform.
This underground shelter you seek is
the most desperate stage for us!
If you're going to be this uncommitted,
just quit.
Fine, I will.
Come on, don't be like that.
I quit.
He can't really quit like that!
I'm heading to the hotel right now.
Let me just get my glasses.
Make yourself at home on the couch.
Okay.
It's sparkling clean.
TIMETABLE
PICK UP EUI-YEONG AT 5 P.M.
DINNER FROM 5:30 TO 7 P.M.
COFFEE FROM 7 TO 7:30 P.M.
MOVIE FOR 90 MINUTES
Oh!
You planned out the whole night?
But...
nothing went as planned.
No.
But
I still had fun.
Feel free to look around if you're bored.
Oh, sure.
Wait.
Do you want a drink?
I have water, sparkling water,
cola, and green tea. What would you like?
I'll have some cold water, please.
Wake up.
What kind of movies do you like?
Anything but horror, really.
Are you scared of horror movies?
They're so bad for my heart.
Are you okay with horror movies?
I can watch them.
When I was younger,
my dad said ghosts weren't scary.
He said people were scarier.
I haven't been scared of ghosts since.
That's a great comment.
I hear that one is good.
- This?
- Yeah.
Should I...
turn off the lights?
Oh, right.
Sure.
This will dry out your hands.
Moisturize them often.
You have to keep them soft.
That's really nice.
Hey...
Ui-yeong.
Yeah?
I have something to tell you.
- Hey.
- Mom!
Oh, my.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Oh, gosh! What do I do?
I'm so sorry!
No, it's fine.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Huh?
Hey! You always eat at my restaurant.
Ma'am!
His father was right.
Humans are the scariest.
THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
IT'S ALREADY TOO LATE
THE BIGGEST PROJECT OF HIS LIFE!
CAN'T STOP BEING NOSY AROUND YOU
I'M GLAD WE MET NOW
THE MEANING OF YOU
SHOULD I TURN OFF THE LIGHTS?
Dating is different now.
In our 20s,
it was just about us two being in love.
Oh, gosh!
Man, I can't stop thinking about it.
If you aren't pretending to read the book
while spying on me
why are you still reading
the table of contents?
Your mom seems to be curious
about how things are going with Ui-yeong.
People will want to know about you
once the news is out.
Reporters will chase you everywhere, too.
Move abroad for school.
Whatever it is...
Stand for what you love.
I want
to fall in love with you.
Subtitles by: Min-sun Kim